marketintellisearch.com 2011-12-22

# Market Intellisearch: Financial news, insight and screeners into market trends and investment sentiment.

This is the Privacy Policy of Market Intellisearch LLC ("Market Intellisearch," or "we") regarding information we collect on our web site ("Site"). Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page for your review. 

1\. **What Information Do We Collect?**

When you visit our Site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and the Site uses information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Site. 

2\. **Personal Information You Choose to Provide**

a. **In General**

We do not collect personally identifiable information about you, except when you provide it to us. For example, if you decide to complete a user registration form or survey, you may be asked to provide certain information such as your contact information (name, e-mail address, mailing address, and telephone number). To protect your personal information, users registering at our Site must also enter a user name and password. 

When you submit your personally identifiable information on our Site, you are giving your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. If you would prefer that we not collect any personally identifiable information from you, please do not provide us with any such information. 

The information you provide may be used by us to create and deliver to you our newsletters, advertisements or surveys, or other similar communications. 

We may use the information you provide in aggregate form for internal business purposes, such as generating statistics and developing marketing plans. We may collect, store or accumulate certain non-personally identifiable information concerning your use of our Site, such as information regarding which of our pages are most popular. We may share or transfer such non-personally identifiable information with or to our affiliates, licensees, advertisers and partners. 

b. **Registration on the Site**

We do not require users to become members of the Site in order to have access to the free news, analysis and commentary available on the Site. If you would like to receive our in- depth analysis, comments, news and updates for over 6000 stocks, stock alerts, and other tools and information available to our registered users, we require you to [register](http://portal.marketintellisearch.com/) to become a member. 

In order to register, you will need to provide us with your email address, name, gender, occupation, annual income, address, and any additional information we may require from time to time. You will also need to choose a unique User Name and Password. You will be required to verify your email address by clicking on an activation link that we will send to you upon registration in order to complete the registration form. 

c. **Subscription Services**

If you would like access to our subscription-based services, you must register as described above. If the subscription service requires paying a fee, you will need to provide your credit card information to PayPal. We do not have access to your credit card information, and all transactions with PayPal are subject to their terms and conditions, as well as their privacy policy. You may review PayPal's [terms and conditions](https://www.paypal.com/us/cgi-bin/marketingweb?cmd=p/gen/ua/ua-outside), as well as their [privacy policy](https://www.paypal.com/us/cgi-bin/marketingweb?cmd=p/gen/ua/policy_privacy-outside). 

3\. **Web Site Use Information**

Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" (see explanation below, "What Are Cookies?") and Web server logs to collect information about how our the Site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site. This information is collected on an aggregate basis. 

You can have your browser notify you of, or automatically reject, cookies. If you reject our cookies, you may still use our Site, but you may be limited in the use of some of the features. Some of our business partners, including third party vendors such as Google, may also use cookies on our Site. However, we have no access to, or control over, these cookies and do not accept any responsibility for such use. 

In addition, we may use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer our Site, track traffic patterns, and gather demographic information for aggregate use, as well as for credit fraud protection and risk reduction. Except as otherwise disclosed in this Privacy Policy, we will not use IP addresses in combination with your personally identifiable information without your prior consent. 

When you visit our Site or view one of our e-mails, we may use pixel tags (also called "clear GIFS" or "clear graphics interchange formats"), tracking links and/or similar technology to note some of the pages you visit on our Site and personalize your experience. We may also use pixel tags to determine what types of e-mail your browser supports. We may use the information collected through pixel tags, tracking links and similar technology in combination with your personally identifiable information. 

4\. **How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?**

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our users. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. The lists used to send you product and service offers are developed and managed under our traditional company standards designed to safeguard the security and privacy of our customers' personal information. As a customer, you will be given the opportunity, at least once annually, to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers. 

We may also retain other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include data analysis firms, customer support specialists, and fulfillment companies. Such third parties may be provided with access to personally identifiable information needed to perform their functions, but may not use such information for any other purpose. 

5\. **What Are Cookies?**

Cookies are a feature of Web browser software that allows Web servers to recognize the computer used to access a Web site. They are small pieces of data that are stored by a user's Web browser on the user's hard drive. Cookies can remember what information a user accesses on one Web page to simplify subsequent interactions with that Web site by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user's transactions on related Web pages. This makes it easier for a user to move from Web page to Web page and to complete commercial transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized. 

6\. **How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?**

We use Web site browser software tools such as cookies and Web server logs to gather information about our Site users' browsing activities in order to constantly improve our Site and better serve our customers. This information assists us to design and arrange our Web pages in the most user-friendly manner and to continually improve our Site to better meet the needs of our customers and prospective customers. 

Cookies help us collect important business and technical statistics. The information in the cookies lets us trace the paths followed by users to our Site as they move from one page to another. Web server logs allow us to count how many people visit our Site and evaluate our Site's visitor capacity. We do not use these technologies to capture your individual e-mail address or any personally identifying information about you although they do permit us to send focused online banner advertisements or other such responses to you. 

7\. **Sharing Information with Outside Companies**

From time to time you may notice offers from outside companies advertised on our Site. We take measures to select product or service providers that are responsible and afford privacy protections to their customers. However, we cannot make any representations about the practices and policies of these companies. 

8\. **Sharing Information with Strategic Partners**

We may enter into strategic marketing alliances or partnerships with third parties who may be given access to personal information including your name, address, telephone number and e-mail for the purpose of providing you information regarding products and services that we think will be of interest to you. In connection with strategic marketing alliances or partnerships, we will retain all ownership rights to the information. 

9\. **Choice/Opt Out**

When you register at this Site, you may opt out of receiving future e-mail communications from us. You may change your e-mail preferences at any time by clicking the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of each e-mail you receive from us. 

10\. **Future Business Transactions**

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell certain of our assets. In such transactions, user information, including personally identifiable information, generally is one of the transferred business assets, and by submitting your personal information on our Site you agree that your data may be transferred to such parties in these circumstances. 

11\. **Notice of New Services and Changes**

Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. As our client, you will be given the opportunity to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by clicking the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of each e-mail you receive from us. 

12\. **How Do We Protect Your Information?**

a. **Evaluation of Information Protection Practices**

Periodically, our operations and business practices are reviewed for compliance with company policies and procedures governing the security, confidentiality and quality of our information. 

b. **Employee Access, Training and Expectations**

Our company values, ethical standards, policies and practices are committed to the protection of customer information. In general, our business practices limit employee access to confidential information, and limit the use and disclosure of such information to authorized persons, processes and transactions. 

13\. **How Can You Access and Correct Your Information?**

You have the ability to review, change and correct the personally identifiable information you provide us. If you are a registered user, you can change your personally identifiable information at any time by clicking the Account Tab on **http://portal.marketintellisearch.com**. 

14\. **Do We Disclose Information to Outside Parties?**

We may provide aggregate information about our customers, sales, Site traffic patterns and related Site information to our affiliates or reputable third parties, but this information will not include personally identifying data, except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy. 

15\. **What About Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information?**

We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights. 

16\. **What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?**

We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Site nor the information or content contained therein. Web Sites may be linked to our Site through advertisements visible on our Site, or through links that we may from time to time provide. Often links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Site. 

Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Site to another Web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other Web site, including Web sites that have a link to our Site, is subject to that Web site's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding. 

17\. **Your Consent**

By using our Site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our Web site to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. As we may make changes at any time without notifying you, we suggest that you periodically consult this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to modify this policy at our sole discretion.
